* [Apps](javascript:void(0))
    
    [Debutify Theme
    
    Built to boost sales and build your brand.
    
    Learn more](https://debutify.com/theme/)
    
    [Debutify Reviews
    
    A simple way to request, collect, and manage reviews.
    
    Learn more](https://debutify.com/reviews/)

* Apps

Privacy Policy
==============

###### Table of contents:

* [How can you review, update, or delete data we collect from you?](#update-information)
* ###### The use of the cookies
    
    * [1\. Type of cookies we use Necessary / Essential Cookies Functionality cookies](#typecookies)

Introduction
------------

With the advent of new communication tools, it is necessary to pay particular attention to the protection of privacy. That is why we, Debutify Inc. (hereinafter “Debutify”), are seriously concerned about your personal information's privacy and are committed to respecting the information we collect.

Debutify undertakes to respect, in accordance with applicable laws, the obligations regarding the collection and processing of personal and confidential information obtained in the context of the operation of a company so that everyone can benefit from the respect of their private life.

The hereby privacy policy (hereinafter the “Policy”) describes the information that Debutify may collect from the user, that is to say, the end-user or the organization you represent or you work for (hereinafter the “User” or “Users”), in connection with its activities, the purposes for which Debutify collects it, the use it makes of it, and the circumstances under which it can pass them on to third parties. In addition, this Policy indicates the User’s rights regarding the collection, use and communication of its personal information. Debutify agrees not to collect, use or disclose the User’s personal information otherwise than in accordance with this Policy and applicable laws in the United States.

Scope of the policy
-------------------

When the User browses Debutify’s website (hereinafter the “Website”), he agrees to the terms and conditions of this Policy. If the User continues to use the Website after a new version of this Policy has been posted here, he consents to and will be bound by the changes.

The information we collect is necessary when we provide the User with a service that he has requested. By providing us with this information, the User consents to its collection and use as defined in this Policy.

Collection of personal information
----------------------------------

Debutify may obtain personal information from the User when he saves his personal information on the Website, or where appropriate, when he discloses this personal information otherwise, such as creating a User account and choosing a password, by logging in as a registered User to the Website, by launching a product search, by requesting a service, by providing information in the account, by contacting us by phone, email or otherwise, or by completing a form to enter a contest, inventory request, promotion or survey.

Do we collect information from minors?
--------------------------------------

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18 or the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Services. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under the age 18, please contact us at [www.debutify.com](https://debutify.com/)

We collect the following User information upon registration:

* The surname and first name;
* The age;
* The gender;
* The telephone number;
* The personal address;
* The email address;
* The bank information;
* The professional address;
* Website

How can you review, update, or delete data we collect from you?
---------------------------------------------------------------

Based on the laws of some countries, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please submit a request by contacting us. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

How long do we keep your information?
-------------------------------------

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will require us to keep your personal information for longer than 7 years.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

Forms and information
---------------------

The User’s personal information may be collected through forms, namely:

* Registration on the website form;
* Order form;
* Update the user's profile form;
* Authorization of the User to access his information; and
* Contact form.

Debutify also uses cookies, as indicated in the “Automatically Exchanged Data” section. Debutify may also keep a record of the User’s product interests and obtain his information from divisions or current or future companies belonging to Debutify.

Debutify may use the User’s personal information to stay in contact with the User and provide him with a personalized service at all times.

If the User has not subscribed to our newsletter, he will not receive any emails from Debutify, except in special cases (i.e. follow-up or expiry of its subscription, follow-up of its free trial, participation in a contest, etc.)

The User’s information is also collected through the interaction that may be established between it and the Website and may be used for the following purposes:

* Provide services to the User;
* Manage customer accounts;
* Sending information letters;
* Contact form;

Advertising information
-----------------------

Debutify will contact you only if you wish. If you prefer not to receive any advertising information from us or if you do not want us to use your personal information to enhance your customer experience, please let us know by contacting us at the contact listed in the section “Right of opposition and withdrawal.”

Remember to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered or when you made a purchase from us. There may be a delay in processing time for a request sent by email or mail, and you may continue to receive communications from Debutify, in the meantime.

What are privacy rights?
------------------------

In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please use the contact details provided below. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal.

Do California residents have specific privacy rights?
-----------------------------------------------------

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we share personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Services, you have the right to request the removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request the removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below. Include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.

Third-party services
--------------------

By using the Platform, the User may engage with third-party applications (hereinafter referred to as “Third-Party Services”).

The User acknowledges and agrees that regardless of how such Third Party Services may be offered to them, Debutify merely acts as an intermediary platform between the User and such Third Party Services, and do not, in any way, endorses Third Party Services or shall be in any way responsible or liable with respect to any such Third Party Services.

The User’s relationship with Third Party Services and any terms governing the User’s payment for, and use of, such Third Party Services, including without limitation, the collection, processing and use of the User’s data by Third Party Services, are subject to a separate contractual arrangement between the User and the provider of a Third Party Service.

Debutify is not a party to, or responsible, in any manner, for the compliance by the User of the Third Party Service.

Through the Platform, the User may enable an integration of the User’s Account with Third Party Services, which will allow an exchange, transmission, modification, or removal of data between Debutify and the Third Party Service, including without limitation, the User’s Data.

The User, hereby acknowledges that any access, collection, transmission, processing, storage, or any other use of data, including the Customer Data, by a Third Party Service is governed by the agreement with the Third Party, including any applicable privacy policy. The User hereby acknowledges that Debutify is not responsible for any access, collection, transmission, processing, storage or any other use of data, including the User’s data, by the Third Party Service or for such Third Party Service privacy and security actions, inaction or general practices.

In no event shall Debutify be liable for any prejudice that may arise from such third-party services. Debutify invites the User to consult these services’ respective website, in order to learn about their conditions of use.

Automatically exchanged data
----------------------------

We collect certain information during exchanges between the User’s computer and our server. Cookies allow the User to connect to the Website.

This information consists mainly of the following:

* Domain name;
* IP address; and
* User's language.

Most of the automatically exchanged data do not allow the identification of the User. They are collected only because of the technological requirements inherent in browsing the internet. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but it is usually possible to modify this setting. However, if the User refuses cookies, he may not be able to identify himself or use certain features of Debutify’s Website.

The use of such information allows us to improve the service, personalize the User’s experience, and better track his requests and orders.

This information is also used to Stay in contact with the User and provide him with a personalized service at all time.

These cookies are multiple; some expire when the User closes his browser and have no effect, while others can be maintained.

International communications
----------------------------

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are accessing our Services from outside United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us in our facilities and by those third parties with whom we may share your personal information in the United States and other countries.

Some countries may not have data protection or other laws as comprehensive as those in Europe, Canada, or the United States. However, we will take all necessary measures to protect your personal information per this privacy policy and applicable law.

\-European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses

Such measures implement the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of personal information between our group companies and between our third-party providers and us, which require all such recipients to protect the personal information that they process from the EEA in accordance with European data protection laws. Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided upon request. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third-party service providers and partners, and further details can be provided upon request.

Sharing personal information
----------------------------

Debutify undertakes not to sell the collected personal data without the User’s explicit consent. Personal data can exclusively be sold in the context of a partial or total disposal of Debutify’s business to a third party. In such situation, the disposed data is subject to the same warranties that those contained in this Confidentiality Policy.

Unless otherwise stated in this Policy, the personal information the User provides will not be transmitted to third parties without his permission. However, we sometimes share this information with partners.

If the User does not wish to have his personal information communicated to third parties or partners, he may opt-out at any time, as mentioned in the following section.

Withdrawal and opposition rights
--------------------------------

We are committed to offering the User the right to oppose and withdraw his personal information.

The right of opposition is understood as the possibility offered to the Users to refuse to allow their personal information to be used for certain purposes mentioned during the collection.

The User also has the right to request access to the personal information we have collected about him and correct any information as needed by contacting the contact person whose information is listed in the “Contact person” section below.

Anti-spam legislation
---------------------

Debutify complies with the United States Anti-Spam Legislation (USASL) dispositions. To withdraw your consent or to stop receiving electronic information or communication, please contact us at the following email address: [\[email protected\]](https://debutify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Security
--------

The personal information Debutify collects is kept in a secure environment. Debutify has taken appropriate measures to maintain the confidentiality of personal information and protect it against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification, taking into account, in particular, its sensitivity and the purposes it is used. In addition, Debutify requires that each employee, proxy, or representative of Debutify complies with this Policy.

To ensure the security of the User’s personal information, Debutify uses the following measures:

* SSL (Secure Sockets Layers) protocol;
* Protected access to servers and computers;
* Confidentiality agreements with its employees;
* Procedures for the protection of personal information;
* Use of password-protected data networks;
* Current update of security measures; and
* Encrypted and secure electronic communications.

Debutify is committed to maintaining a high degree of confidentiality by incorporating the latest technological innovations to ensure the confidentiality of the User’s transactions to protect the User’s personal information and prevent it from being viewed, used, or disclosed without authorization.

However, since no mechanism provides maximum security, some risk is always present when communicating personal information via the internet. If a password is used to protect the User’s account and personal information, it is his responsibility to keep it confidential.

Data breach
-----------

A privacy breach occurs when there is unauthorized access to or collection, use, disclosure, or disposal of personal information. You will be notified about data breaches when Debutify believes you are likely to be at risk of serious harm. For example, a data breach may likely result in serious financial harm or harm to your mental or physical well-being. In the event that Debutify becomes aware of a security breach that has resulted or may result in unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of personal information, Debutify will promptly investigate the matter and notify the applicable Supervisory Authority not later than 72 hours after having become aware of it, unless the personal data breach is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of natural persons.

Applicable laws and jurisdiction
--------------------------------

The Website and its content are managed by Debutify from their offices located in the province of the United States. The Website, its content, the Terms of Use and your use of the Website are regulated by the applicable legislation of the United States, without giving effect to no principle regarding conflicts of laws.

You accept that any question or litigation regarding the Platform and your use of it will first be brought before a mediator and, in the absence of a compromise, settled by the courts of the province of the United States.

If the User is a consumer under the United States Consumer Protection Act, then any litigation will be ruled by the law of the Province of United States, and the competent jurisdiction will be determined according to the rules of the Code of Civil Procedure.

Interpretation
--------------

This Policy is governed by applicable United States laws, including the Privacy Act of United States. These laws apply without giving effect to any conflict of law principles.

Whenever the context so requires, any word written in the singular also includes the plural and vice versa; any word written in the masculine gender also includes the feminine gender and vice versa.

Divisibility
------------

Each provision of this Policy is a separate and distinct whole so that a court decision that any provision of this Policy is invalid or unenforceable will not affect the validity or enforceability of the remaining provisions of this Policy.

Amendment of this policy
------------------------

We occasionally update this Policy. Continued use of this Platform constitutes the User’s agreement to this Policy and its updates.

Debutify reserves the right to modify or supplement this Policy at any time, at its sole discretion and without notice.

If you object to any changes to this Policy, please cease all use of the Website. Debutify will attempt, as much as possible, to inform Users of any changes to this Policy, However, it is the User’s responsibility to review it regularly to be informed of any changes that may be made. However, Debutify will notify prior to the effective date of the amendment to the current Policy. Debutify will notify the User by sending an email informing the User that it has published the details of the changes on its Website. If the User does not accept these changes and no longer wishes to use the Website, the User must cease all use of the Website.

Cookie policy terms
-------------------

This Cookies Policy explains what Cookies are and how We use them. You should read this policy so You can understand what type of cookies We use, or the information We collect using Cookies and how that information is used.

Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about You may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from Cookies. For further information on how We use, store and keep your personal data secure, see our Privacy Policy.

We do not store sensitive personal information, such as mailing addresses, account passwords, etc. in the Cookies We use.  
The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.

The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or plural.

Definition
----------

For the purposes of this Cookies Policy:

* Website (referred to as either “We”, “Us” or “Our” in this Cookies Policy) refers to [Debutify.com](https://debutify.com/)
* You means the individual accessing or using the Website, or any legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Website, as applicable.
* Cookies are small files placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing details of your browsing history on that website among its many uses.
* Website refers to Debutify, accessible from [www.debutify.com](https://www.debutify.com/)

The use of the cookies
----------------------

### 1\. Type of cookies we use

Cookies can be “Persistent” or “Session” Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close your web browser.

We use both session and persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

#### Necessary / Essential Cookies

Type: Session Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.

#### Functionality cookies

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.

### 2\. Your choice regarding cookies

If You prefer to avoid the use of Cookies on the Website, first You must disable the use of Cookies in your browser and then delete the Cookies saved in your browser associated with this website. You may use this option to prevent the use of Cookies at any time.

If You do not accept Our Cookies, You may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Website and some features may not function properly.

Most web browsers, mobile operating systems, and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference and not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy policy.

If You’d like to delete Cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse Cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

* For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from
* Google: [https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050)
* For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from
* Microsoft: [http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835](http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835)
* For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from
* Mozilla: [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored)
* For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from
* Apple: [https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)

For any other web browser, please visit your web browser’s official web pages.

#### More information about cookies

You can learn more about Cookies at the following third-party websites:

* Network Advertising Initiative: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

Contact
-------

You may exercise your rights provided in this Policy, or you may address any other question or complaint regarding Debutify’s privacy practices by contacting us:

E-mail: [\[email protected\]](https://debutify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### Scale your brand effortlessly with Debutify

Copyright 2024 Debutify Corp. All rights reserved.

* * *

Subscribe to our newsletter

Sign up now and get updates on the latest eCommerce trends, news, and tips.

Subscribe

Customer Service

[\[email protected\]](https://debutify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Sales

[\[email protected\]](https://debutify.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* * *

* Product

* Company

* Resources

* Support

* * *

* * *

We use cookies to personalize our website for you and help collect analytics to create a better browsing experience.

Accept

Decline
